<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<company>
  <title>Vittoria Games</title>
  <based-in>Cambridge MA, United States</based-in>
  <founding-date>June 2022</founding-date>
  <website></website>
  <press-contact>vittoriagamestudio@gmail.com

  </press-contact>

  <!-- Google analytics ID: -->
  <!-- <analytics></analytics> -->

  <phone></phone>
  <address>
    <line>891 Massachusetts Ave, Apt 14</line>
    <line>Cambridge, MA 02139</line>
    <line>United States</line>
  </address>

  <socials>
    <social>
      <name>Twitter @vittoriagames</name>
      <link>https://twitter.com/vittoriagames</link>
    </social>
    <social>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44138548</link>
    </social>
  </socials>

  <widgets>
    <mailchimp>58d170f741</mailchimp>
    <steam>44138548</steam>
  </widgets>

  <description>
    Hi, I'm Nick Francisci and I run Vittoria Games, a solo-dev studio creating deep strategy and management games. My debut game is Forum Mortuorum, a gladiator managment game where you take control of a gladiator school as you fight your way up the Medterranean leagues whilst encountering foes both mortal and mythological.
  </description>

  <history>
    I'm a part-time dev, chasing a passion of combining my software-eningeering training and my artistic streak to makes deep management games I'd love to play.

    On the way to creating Forum Mortuorum, I've worked on or collaborated on several game projects that never made it to full production. In the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic, my girlfriend and I began a multiplayer city-builder featuring goats as citizens. Though we made it to a playable early build, we eventually abandoned the project. Following that, I worked with a friend and fellow software engineer on a dieselpunk co-operative RPG in which you crewed a flying battleship. Unfortunately, that project proved too great for our modest means.

    From these projects, Forum Mortuorum emerged with a simple charter: a game I could finish as a solo-dev. Though far from done, I have every confidence that it will debut in 2024 and act as the foundation for Vittoria Games' future.
  </history>


  <!-- Or multiple blocks: -->
  <!--
  <histories>
    <history>
      <header></header>
      <text></text>
    </history>
  </histories>
  -->

<!--   <trailers>
    <trailer>
      <name></name>

      <youtube>
      </youtube>
      <vimeo>
      </vimeo>
    </trailer>
  </trailers>

  <awards>
    <award>
      <description></description>
      <info></info>
    </award>
  </awards>

  <quotes>
    <quote>
      <description></description>
      <name></name>
      <website></website>
      <link></link>
    </quote>
  </quotes> -->

<!--   <additionals>
    <additional>
      <title></title>
      <description></description>
      <link></link>
    </additional>
  </additionals> -->

  <credits>
    <credit>
      <person>Nick Francisci</person>
      <role>Founder, Jack-of-All-Trades</role>
      <website>http://www.nickfrancisci.com</website>
    </credit>
  </credits>
<!--
   <contacts>
    <contact>
      <name></name>

     <mail></mail>
      <link></link>
    </contact>
  </contacts> -->
</company>
